Guide to Tuli Kupferberg and Sylvia Topp Papers MSS.385
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series IV. Projects, 1959-2009, undated; 28 Linear Feet in 5 record cartons, 38 manuscript boxes, 6 flat boxes, 3 hinged-ring binder boxes, 6 oversize folders, 1 flat-file folder; 3 sound discs (vinyl); 2 sound discs (cd); 2 dvd-r disks; 86 sound tape reels; 273 audiocassettes; 2 sound cassettes (
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Bush Inauguration [Part 2], 2001-03-07; cuid20791 (Box 312, Cassette MNN 0336)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Cannon's Mouth, circa 1996-2007; cuid20792 (Box 304, Cassette MNN 0005)
    Format: MiniDV, Duration: 2 min.
  - Revolting News Television Show -- CB Inaug [Part 2], 2001-03-21; cuid20793 (Box 312, Cassette MNN 0337)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- CB Inaug [Part 3], 2001-03-21; cuid20794 (Box 312, Cassette MNN 0339)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- CBGB's Benefit [Part 1], circa 1996-2007; cuid20795 (Box 311, Cassette MNN 0043)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- CBGB's Benefit [Part 2], circa 1996-2007; cuid20796 (Box 311, Cassette MNN 0044)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Chomsky [Part 1], circa 1996-2007; cuid20797 (Box 311, Cassette MNN 0174)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Chomsky [Part 2], circa 1996-2007; cuid20798 (Box 311, Cassette MNN 0179)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Chomsky [Part 3], circa 1996-2007; cuid20799 (Box 311, Cassette MNN 0187)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Civility, Sam Smith, circa 1996-2007; cuid20800 (Box 311, Cassette MNN 0234)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Clinton/Diaspora/Labor, circa 1996-2007; cuid20801 (Box 311, Cassette MNN 0272)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Clinton-Monica Show [Part 1], circa 1996-2007; cuid20802 (Box 311, Cassette MNN 0274)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Clinton-Monica Show [Part 2], circa 1996-2007; cuid20803 (Box 311, Cassette MNN 0275)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Crimes of the Beats, Skinhead Music, 1993-05-29; cuid20804 (Box 304, Cassette MNN 0002)
    Format: VHS, Duration: 164 min. Preservation Note: Occasional video dropouts.
    This tape includes multiple 30min episodes of the same documented event about the Beats, as well as one episode of MTV News production featuring Kurt Loder on "racist skinheads" in punk and rock music.
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Danny Schechter [Part 1], 1999-05-26; cuid20805 (Box 313, Cassette MNN 0387)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Danny Schechter [Part 2], 1999-05-26; cuid20806 (Box 313, Cassette MNN 0388)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Dave McReynolds, Prez Campaign, 2000-11-01; cuid20807 (Box 312, Cassette MNN 0328)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- David Amram, LES [Part 3], 2002-04-03; cuid20808 (Box 313, Cassette MNN 0379)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- David Amram's Vibrations, 2001-06-27; cuid20809 (Box 312, Cassette MNN 0357)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Dialectics Bertell Ollman [Part 2], circa 1996-2007; cuid20810 (Box 311, Cassette MNN 0057)
    Format: VHS, Duration: 30 min. Preservation Note: Occasional static and video dropouts.
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Diane Spodarek Show, 2001-12-26; cuid20811 (Box 312, Cassette MNN 0372)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Ed Sanders 65th Birthday [Part 1], 2006-02-21; cuid20812 (Box 304, Cassette MNN 0501)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Ed Sanders 65th Birthday [Part 2], 2006-03-07; cuid20813 (Box 304, Cassette MNN 0502)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Ed Sanders and Tuli Kupferberg, Bowery Poetry Club [Part 1], 2005-08-26; cuid20814 (Box 304, Cassette MNN 0010)
    Format: MiniDV, Duration: 32 min.
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Ed Sanders and Tuli Kupferberg, Bowery Poetry Club [Part 2], 2005-08-26; cuid20815 (Box 304, Cassette MNN 0011)
    Format: MiniDV, Duration: 60min.
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Election, 2008-05-19; cuid20816 (Box 304, Cassette MNN 0566)
    Format: MiniDV, Duration: 30 min.
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Election [Part 2], circa 1996-2007; cuid20817 (Box 311, Cassette MNN 0214)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Election '98, 2000-11-29; cuid20818 (Box 312, Cassette MNN 0330)
    Format: VHS, Duration: 31 min.
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Election Night Folly '96 at the Brecht Forum [Part 1], 1996; cuid20819 (Box 311, Cassette MNN 0220)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Election Night Folly '96 at the Brecht Forum [Part 2], 1996; cuid20820 (Box 311, Cassette MNN 0221)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Election Night Folly '96 at the Brecht Forum [Part 3], 1996; cuid20821 (Box 311, Cassette MNN 0222)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Eric Drooker and Flood [Part 1], circa 1996-2007; cuid20822 (Box 313, Cassette MNN 0408)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Eric Drooker and Flood [Part 2], circa 1996-2007; cuid20823 (Box 313, Cassette MNN 0411)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Eric Drooker at ABC NORIO [Part 1], 1996-09-22; cuid20824 (Box 313, Cassette MNN 0463)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Eric Drooker at ABC NORIO [Part 2], 1996-09-29; cuid20825 (Box 313, Cassette MNN 0445)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Eric Drooker at ABC NORIO [Part 3], 1996-10-06; cuid20826 (Box 313, Cassette MNN 0464)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Fugs History, Ed and Tuli [Part 1], 2005-12-27; cuid20827 (Box 304, Cassette MNN 0457)
    Format: VHS, Duration: 28 min.
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Fugs History, Ed and Tuli [Part 2], 2006-01-10; cuid20828 (Box 304, Cassette MNN 0498)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Fugs History, Ed and Tuli [Part 3], 2006-01-24; cuid20829 (Box 304, Cassette MNN 0499)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Gringo in Mañanaland [Part 1], circa 1996-2007; cuid20830 (Box 311, Cassette MNN 0188)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Gringo in Mañanaland [Part 2], circa 1996-2007; cuid20831 (Box 311, Cassette MNN 0189)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Howard Zinn on the History of Freedom of Speech in America [Part 1], 1996-10-27; cuid20832 (Box 311, Cassette MNN 0228)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Howard Zinn on the History of Freedom of Speech in America [Part 2], 1996-11-10; cuid20833 (Box 311, Cassette MNN 0233)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Howl Poetry Festival [Part 1], 2004-03-30; cuid20834 (Box 313, Cassette MNN 0438)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Howl Poetry Festival [Part 2], 2004-04-13; cuid20835 (Box 313, Cassette MNN 0439)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Howl Poetry Festival, Allen Ginsberg Tompkins Square Park [Part 1], 2003-10-29; cuid20836 (Box 313, Cassette MNN 0420)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Israel, 2009-06-26; cuid20837 (Box 304, Cassette MNN 0577)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Izzy Young [Part 1], 1997-02-16; cuid20838 (Box 313, Cassette MNN 0413)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Izzy Young [Part 2], 1997-02-23; cuid20839 (Box 313, Cassette MNN 0447)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Izzy Young [Part 3], 1997-03-02; cuid20840 (Box 313, Cassette MNN 0448)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Izzy Young [Part 4], 1997-03-09; cuid20841 (Box 313, Cassette MNN 0449)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Jeff and Jack, BlueStocking, 2006-06-03; cuid20842 (Box 304, Cassette MNN 0017)
    Format: MiniDV, Duration: 38 min.
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Jeff Lewis, Helen Schreiner Shop, Cake, 2007-06-04; cuid20843 (Box 304, Cassette MNN 0541)
    Format: VHS, Duration: 27 min.
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Judith Malina, Poetry Reading [Part 1], 2002-03-06; cuid20844 (Box 313, Cassette MNN 0440)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Judith Malina, Poetry Reading [Part 2], 2002-03-20; cuid20845 (Box 313, Cassette MNN 0441)
    Format: VHS, Duration: 28 min. Preservation Note: Video dropouts throughout.
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Lenni Brenner [Part 1], circa 1996-2007; cuid20846 (Box 312, Cassette MNN 0277)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Lenni Brenner [Part 2], circa 1996-2007; cuid20847 (Box 312, Cassette MNN 0278)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Liedown Comedy of Tuli the K, circa 1996-2007; cuid20848 (Box 311, Cassette MNN 0267)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Linc Picks, 2008-04-03; cuid20849 (Box 304, Cassette MNN 0563)
    Format: MiniDV, Duration: 31 min.
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Living Theater [Part 1], circa 1996-2007; cuid20850 (Box 311, Cassette MNN 0087)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Living Theater [Part 2], circa 1996-2007; cuid20851 (Box 311, Cassette MNN 0088)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Loisaida Fest, Jeff Lewis, Richie Heisler, Paul Thornton, 2006-05-28; cuid20852 (Box 304, Cassette MNN 0014)
    Format: MiniDV, Duration: 35 min.
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Loudon Wainwright [Part 1], 2008-11-17; cuid20853 (Box 304, Cassette MNN 0579)
    Format: MiniDV, Duration: 29 min.
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Loudon Wainwright [Part 2], 2008-12-01; cuid20854 (Box 304, Cassette MNN 0580)
    Format: MiniDV, Duration: 24 min.
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Loudon Wainwright [Part 3], 2008-12-15; cuid20855 (Box 304, Cassette MNN 0581)
    Format: MiniDV, Duration: 23 min.
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Music and Madness, 1998-02-04; cuid20856 (Box 311, Cassette MNN 0257)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- New Movement and "Violence", Dave McReynolds, 2000-11-15; cuid20857 (Box 312, Cassette MNN 0329)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- New Years at St. Marks Poetry Project [Part 1], 1999; cuid20858 (Box 311, Cassette MNN 0255)
    Format: VHS, Duration: 8 min.
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Nobody for President, circa 1996-2007; cuid20859 (Box 304, Cassette MNN 0015)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- On the Media [Part 1], 2007-02-26; cuid20860 (Box 304, Cassette MNN 0534)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Parasong [Part 1], 2007-04-30; cuid20861 (Box 304, Cassette MNN 0008)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Parasong [Part 1], 2007-05-07; cuid20862 (Box 304, Cassette MNN 0539)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Parasong [Part 2], 2007-04-30; cuid20863 (Box 304, Cassette MNN 0009)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Parasongs [Part 1], 2007-03-12; cuid20864 (Box 304, Cassette MNN 0535)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Parasongs [Part 2], 2007-03-26; cuid20865 (Box 304, Cassette MNN 0536)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Parasongs [Part 2], 2007-05-21; cuid20866 (Box 304, Cassette MNN 0540)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Penny Arcade [Part 1], 2001-07-11; cuid20867 (Box 312, Cassette MNN 0353)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Penny Arcade [Part 2], 2001-07-25; cuid20868 (Box 312, Cassette MNN 0354)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Penny/Galact, 2002-02-02; cuid20869 (Box 313, Cassette MNN 0376)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Pete Stampfel and Jeff Lewis [Part 1], 2008-01-14; cuid20870 (Box 304, Cassette MNN 0557)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Pete Stampfel and Jeff Lewis [Part 2], 2008-01-28; cuid20871 (Box 304, Cassette MNN 0558)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Peter L. Wilson, Europe [Part 2], circa 1996-2007; cuid20872 (Box 311, Cassette MNN 0247)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Peter L. Wilson, U.S. [Part 1], circa 1996-2007; cuid20873 (Box 311, Cassette MNN 0246)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Peter L. Wilson, World Issues [Part 3], circa 1996-2007; cuid20874 (Box 311, Cassette MNN 0249)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- PoPro [Part 1], 2009-02-09; cuid20875 (Box 304, Cassette MNN 0582)
    Format: MiniDV, Duration: 30min.
    This recording features Ron Padgett, Yuko Otomo, Nicole Peyrafitte, Thaddeus Rutkowski, Wanda Phipps, and Maria Mirabel.
  - Revolting News Television Show -- PoPro [Part 2], 2009-02-23; cuid20876 (Box 304, Cassette MNN 0593)
    This recording features Pattie Smith, Steve Taylor, Bob Holman, Steve Earle, Merle Lisker, Bill Kushner, Taylor Meade, Lenny Kaye, and Jonas Mekas.
  - Revolting News Television Show -- PoPro [Part 3], 2009-03-09; cuid20877 (Box 304, Cassette MNN 0594)
    This recording features C. A. Conard, Hettie Jones, Hal Sirowitz, Sylvia Gorelick, Foamola, Chris Rael, and Anselm Berrigan.
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Punk, 2007-01-01; cuid20878 (Box 304, Cassette MNN 0530)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Republican National Convention [Part 1], 2001-10-12; cuid20879 (Box 313, Cassette MNN 0451)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Republican National Convention [Part 2], 2001-10-12; cuid20880 (Box 313, Cassette MNN 0452)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Republican National Convention [Part 3], 2004-10-26; cuid20881 (Box 313, Cassette MNN 0453)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Republican National Convention [Part 4], 2004-11-09; cuid20882 (Box 313, Cassette MNN 0454)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Sander Hicks and Culture of the Left [Part 1], 2000-05-31; cuid20883 (Box 312, Cassette MNN 0317)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Sander Hicks and Culture of the Left [Part 2], 2000-06-14; cuid20884 (Box 312, Cassette MNN 0318)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Sander Hicks and Culture of the Left [Part 3], 2000-06-28; cuid20885 (Box 312, Cassette MNN 0319)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Sander Hicks and Culture of the Left [Part 4], 2000-07-12; cuid20886 (Box 312, Cassette MNN 0320)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Serbian War [Part 1], circa 1996-2007; cuid20887 (Box 312, Cassette MNN 0288)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Serbian War [Part 2], circa 1996-2007; cuid20888 (Box 312, Cassette MNN 0289)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Sermon and Song [Part 2], circa 1996-2007; cuid20889 (Box 311, Cassette MNN 0269)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Shimmy, Knitting Factory, 2000-07-27; cuid20890 (Box 312, Cassette MNN 0323)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Socialist Scholar's Conference [Part 1], 1996-06-09; cuid20891 (Box 311, Cassette MNN 0193)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Socialist Scholar's Conference [Part 2], 1996-06-23; cuid20892 (Box 311, Cassette MNN 0194)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Socialist Scholar's Conference [Part 3], 1996-07-07; cuid20893 (Box 311, Cassette MNN 0195)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Socialist Scholar's Conference [Part 4], 1996; cuid20894 (Box 311, Cassette MNN 0196)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Sparrow Poetry, 2002-01-09; cuid20895 (Box 313, Cassette MNN 0373)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- St. Mark's 2004 New Year's [Part 1], 2004-01-21; cuid20896 (Box 313, Cassette MNN 0426)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- St. Mark's 2004 New Year's [Part 2], 2004-02-04; cuid20897 (Box 313, Cassette MNN 0427)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- St. Mark's 2004 New Year's [Part 3], 2004-02-18; cuid20898 (Box 313, Cassette MNN 0428)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- St. Mark's 2004 New Year's [Part 4], 2004-03-03; cuid20899 (Box 313, Cassette MNN 0429)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- St. Mark's 2004 New Year's [Part 5], 2004-03-17; cuid20900 (Box 313, Cassette MNN 0430)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- St. Mark's Poetry, 1999; cuid20901 (Box 313, Cassette MNN 0474)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- St. Mark's Poetry, 1999; cuid20902 (Box 312, Cassette MNN 0309)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Steven Ben Israel - A Séance to Contact The Living, circa 1996-2007; cuid20903 (Box 311, Cassette MNN 0262)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Stolen Lives Project, circa 1996-2007; cuid20904 (Box 312, Cassette MNN 0301)
    Format: VHS, Duration: 30min. Preservation Note: Audio in right channel only.
  - Revolting News Television Show -- The Fugs at Woodstock '99 [Part 1], 1999; cuid20905 (Box 312, Cassette MNN 0299)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- The Fugs at Woodstock '99 [Part 2], 1999; cuid20906 (Box 312, Cassette MNN 0300)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- The Fugs Live at Byrdcliff [Part 1], 1999-09-15; cuid20907 (Box 312, Cassette MNN 0302)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- The Fugs Live at Byrdcliff [Part 2], 1999-09-29; cuid20908 (Box 312, Cassette MNN 0303)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- The Poetry of John S. Hall, 1996-11-17; cuid20909 (Box 313, Cassette MNN 0396)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- TNC LES Fest, Penny and Tuli [Part 2], 1999; cuid20910 (Box 313, Cassette MNN 0401)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- TNC LES Fest, Penny [Part 1], 1999; cuid20911 (Box 313, Cassette MNN 0400)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- TNC LES Fest, Stephan Smith [Part 3], 2004-01-07; cuid20912 (Box 313, Cassette MNN 0425)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- TNC LES Fest, Tuli + Steve Ben, 2003-07-09; cuid20913 (Box 313, Cassette MNN 0412)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Triangle Shirtwaist Factory Fire Memorial, 2007-03-26; cuid20914 (Box 304, Cassette MNN 0012)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Triangle Shirtwaist Factory Fire Memorial, 2007-04-23; cuid20915 (Box 304, Cassette MNN 0538)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Tsaura Litzky, 2000-03-04; cuid20916 (Box 311, Cassette MNN 0259)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Tuli and Jeff Lewis Interview [Part 2], 2006-06-08; cuid20917 (Box 304, Cassette MNN 0608)
    Format: MiniDV, Duration: 62 min.
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Tuli + Judson [Part 1], 1999-04-20; cuid20918 (Box 312, Cassette MNN 0312)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Tuli + Judson [Part 2], 1999-04-20; cuid20919 (Box 312, Cassette MNN 0313)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Tuli and Jeff, 2006-03-20; cuid20920 (Box 304, Cassette MNN 0019)
    Format: MiniDV, Duration: 53 min.
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Tuli and Lanny, 2002-09-28; cuid20921 (Box 304, Cassette MNN 0018)
    Format: MiniDV, Duration: 40 min. Preservation Note: Audio in left channel only.
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Tuli Channels Marx, 2009-01-26; cuid20922 (Box 304, Cassette MNN 0001)
    Format: MiniDV, Duration: 10 min.
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Tuli LES Festival and Joe Franklin [Part 1], 2000; cuid20923 (Box 312, Cassette MNN 0358)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Tuli LES Festival and Joe Franklin [Part 2], 2000; cuid20924 (Box 312, Cassette MNN 0366)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Tuli on Media, circa 1996-2007; cuid20925 (Box 304, Cassette MNN 0004)
    Format: MiniDV, Duration: 30 min. Preservation Note: There are some lost frames from 00:05:25-00:05:55.
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Tuli, Perv, 2007-12-31; cuid20926 (Box 304, Cassette MNN 0576)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Volcano - Krassner, 1993-11; cuid20927 (Box 304, Cassette MNN 0000)
    Format: VHS, Duration: 87 min.
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Warhol/Lenny Bruce YouTube, 2008; cuid20928 (Box 304, Cassette MNN 0013)
    Format: MiniDV, Duration: 3 min.
  - Revolting News Television Show -- When the Mode of Music Changes, 2003-02-06; cuid20929 (Box 304, Cassette MNN 0016)
    Format: MiniDV, Duration: 5 min.
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Woodstock 2004, cuid20930 (Box 304, Cassette MNN 0002)
    Format: MiniDV, Duration: 48 min.
  - Revolting News Television Show -- You're Insane, History of the Constitution, Sermon and Song, NY NY, circa 1996-2007; cuid20931 (Box 312, Cassette MNN 0287)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Zinn 30's and 60's [Part 1], 1996; cuid20932 (Box 311, Cassette MNN 0202)
  - Revolting News Television Show -- Other Videos, 1992-2009, undated (Box 314, Box 315, Box 316, Vhs 385_034, 385_035, 385_036, 385_037, 385_038, 385_039, 385_040, 385_041, 385_042, 385_043, 385_044, 385_045, 385_046, 385_047, 385_048, 385_050, 385_051, 385_052, 385_053, 385_054, 385_055, 385_056, 385_057, 385_058, 385_059, Box 317, U-matic 385_079, 385_080, 385_081, 385_082, 385_083, Box 204, Box 207, Vhs 385_060, 385_061, 385_062, 385_063, 385_064, 385_065, 385_066, 385_067, 385_068, 385_069, 385_070, 385_071, 385_072, 385_073, 385_074, 385_075, 385_076, 385_077, 385_078)
  - Revolting Theater, 1960s-1980s, undated (Box 179, Folder 2-18, Box 180, Folder 1-12, Box 181, Folder 1-9, Box 147, Folder 7, Flat-file-folder 4, Box 210, Box 326, Folder 2)
  - Revolting Theater -- Video, 1995 (Box 316, Vhs 385_049, Box 204)
  - Rot is Deeper Than You Think, Undated; cuid34760 (Box 204, Quarter inch audio reel 385_113)
  - Royalty Statements and Contracts, 1967-1970 (Box 181, Folder 10)
  - RPI Slide Show, 1994 (Box 181, Folder 11)
  - Sandy and Street Kids, Undated; cuid34740 (Box 208, Quarter inch audio reel 385_031)
  - Serenade - Carmen Dragon conducting the Capitol Symphony Orchestra, Undated; cuid34739 (Box 208, Quarter inch audio reel 385_030)
  - Shimmy Disc Contracts, 1998 (Box 181, Folder 12)
  - Show Notes, Setlists, Appearance Schedules, etc., 1982-2005 (Box 181, Folder 13-16, Box 182, Folder 1-5)
  - Show Songs, Poems, Notes, undated (Box 182, Folder 6)
  - Silvia Thins, 1st Version (O Sole Mio), Undated; cuid34795 (Box 204, Quarter inch audio reel 385_148)
  - Smoking Show -- Notes, 1993-1998, undated (Box 182, Folder 7)
  - Social Studies, Undated; cuid34774 (Box 204, Quarter inch audio reel 385_127)
  - Social Studies, Undated; cuid34777 (Box 204, Quarter inch audio reel 385_130)
  - Song Show, undated (Box 182, Folder 8)
  - Sound Recordings on Cassette, 1978-2003, undated (Box 199, Box 200, Box 201, Box 202, Box 203)
  - Sound Recordings on Digital Audio Tape, undated (Box 203)
  - Sound Recordings on Disc, 1989-1990 (Box 205)
  - Sound Recordings on Disc (CD), 1966, 1989 (Box 205)
  - Spade Song, January 1967; cuid34757 (Box 204, Quarter inch audio reel 385_110)
  - St. Mark's -- New Year's, 2002, 2003, undated (Box 182, Folder 9-10)
  - Street 1959 -- Materials Found on NYC Streets; 1st Show; 2nd Show (Box 182, Folder 11-13)
  - The Strolling Players, Undated; cuid34764 (Box 204, Quarter inch audio reel 385_117)
  - Surely the People is Grass, Undated; cuid34755 (Box 204, Quarter inch audio reel 385_108)
  - Surgeon Spare That Cock, August 1968; cuid34754 (Box 204, Quarter inch audio reel 385_107)
  - Swami, London, Whore of Babylon, Mourn Not the Dead - Produced by Kramer at Noise New York, 1986; cuid34736 (Box 208, Quarter inch audio reel 385_023)
  - Sweet Singer of Bleecker Street, Undated; cuid34783 (Box 204, Quarter inch audio reel 385_136)
  - Tamiment Library Show, 2004 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Tamizdat -- The Plastic People of the Universe (Event), at Irving Plaza, 1998 (Box 183, Folder 2)
  - Teach Yourself Fucking, 1992, undated (Box 183, Folder 3-5)
  - Teen Faggot, 1965; cuid34751 (Box 204, Quarter inch audio reel 385_104)
  - Test Tape, Undated; cuid34738 (Box 208, Quarter inch audio reel 385_029)
  - Theater for the New City -- Lower East Side, 2003 (Box 183, Folder 6)
  - Theater of the Real -- Videos, 1989-1991; cuid34716 (Box 317, U-matic 385_087, 385_088, 385_089, 385_090, 385_091, 385_092, Box 316, U-matic 385_093, 385_094)
  - Times Change Press Agreements, Correspondence, 1971-1973 (Box 183, Folder 7)
  - Tonic, 2000 (Box 183, Folder 8)
  - Top of the Village Gate, 1988-1990 (Box 183, Folder 9)
  - Tour -- British and Dutch Brochures, circa 1992 (Box 183, Folder 10)
  - Tuli - All the Hippy People, Undated; cuid34743 (Box 204, Quarter inch audio reel 385_096, 385_109)
  - Tuli - Children of the Dream, Undated; cuid34778 (Box 204, Quarter inch audio reel 385_131)
  - Tuli - Flower Children, Undated; cuid34744 (Box 204, Quarter inch audio reel 385_097)
  - Tuli - Flower Passion, Undated; cuid34776 (Box 204, Quarter inch audio reel 385_129)
  - Tuli - Sandy and Kids, Undated; cuid34748 (Box 204, Quarter inch audio reel 385_101)
  - Tuli - Surely the People is Grass, Undated; cuid34758 (Box 204, Quarter inch audio reel 385_111)
  - Tuli - Sweet Singer of Bleecker Street, Undated; cuid34785 (Box 204, Quarter inch audio reel 385_138)
  - Tuli and Friends Album, 1965-1992, undated (Box 183, Folder 11-14)